# Benjamin Boswick

4th Year Environmental Design - Landscape + Urbanism Student

A hard-working individual who effectively prioritizes tasks, operating in both independent and group settings. With intense dedication towards academics, a consistent work ethic is displayed. Keeping an open mind is necessary for creativity and retaining new information and experiences in the field.

_			
$( \cap r)$	いけってけ	Inform	ation
$\sim$ 01	Hatt		iauvii

## Education

**Email** 

ben.boswick@gmail.com

Website

https://boswick.design

Experience

2017/05 -

2015/02 -

2016/10

2019/11

<sup>2018/09</sup> B. Env.D., University of Manitoba 2021/05

Sales Associate

Direct customer service

2016/09 -University 1/Faculty of Science, University of Manitoba 2018/05

<sup>2010/09</sup> High School Graduate, Grant Park High School 2016/06

McMunn and Yates Building Supplies (600 Pembina Highway)

Operated and maintained necessary machinery

Provided ancillary services outside and off-site

Tactful handling of challenging situations

Assembled merchandising displays

Created and managed sales orders through a Point of Sales system

• Developed quotes for various products and structural packages

• Attained knowledge of an array of products in every department

### Hard Skills

Microsoft Office

Adobe InDesign

Adobe Photoshop

Rhino3D

AutoCAD

SketchUp

Adobe Illustrator

**VectorWorks** 

Soft Skills

Communication

Interpersonal Skills

Time Management

Collaboration

## **Associations**

#### 2020-21 Student Mentorship Program Cofounder

University of Manitoba Faculty of Architecture Partners Program

- Coordinating student mentoring groups
- Ensuring success of participating mentors and mentees

#### 2020-21 Student Mentor and Ambassador

University of Manitoba Faculty of Architecture Partners Program

- Providing advice and guidance to peers
- Participating as a faculty representative in various events

#### 2020-21 **Graduation Committee Treasurer**

University of Manitoba Faculty of Architecture Student Architecture Society

- Managing committee finances
- Communicating and maintaining faculty wear inventory

#### 2019-21 Student Affiliate

Manitoba Association of Landscape Architects (MALA)

### Dedication

**Problem Solvina** 

#### Estimation

Merchandising

## **Publications**

2019-20 "Urban Orchard", Warehouse Journal, Vol. 29 (Individual Project)

2018-19 "Untitled", Warehouse Journal, Vol. 28 (Collaborative Project)